krtmarketing.com 2019-02-24

# KRT Marketing | Privacy Policy

We at KRT Marketing, Inc. and our affiliates are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to our websites, including www.krtmarketing.com, [www.vet.careers](http://www.vet.careers/), [www.ilovetalentacquisition.com](https://www.ilovetalentacquisition.com/). This Privacy Policy governs our data collection, processing and usage practices. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. By using the Websites, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Websites. 

We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically.

Before providing any personal information and navigating our websites, please read this policy. By accessing the Websites and providing us with your information, you agree with this policy. If you have questions about this document, please email us at: [privacy@krtmarketing.com](mailto:privacy@krtmarketing.com)

* * *

### OUR COMMITMENT TO USER PRIVACY AND DATA PROTECTION

* * *

We don’t sell, rent or make public your private information. If we are co-hosting events with other companies and information will be shared, this will be clearly informed upon data collection.

* * *

### WHAT DATA WE COLLECT AND WHY

* * *

##### TRACKING OF WEBSITE VISITS

How  
The Websites listed above use Google Analytics (GA) to track user engagement. GA automatically records geographical location, device type, internet browser and operating system (OS), but none of this information personally identifies you. GA also records your computer’s IP address which could personally identify you, but we do not have access to that information.

Please check [Google’s developer guides](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage) to learn more about how GA uses cookies.

The KRT Marketing Websites also use the following track codes: 

  * [HubSpot](https://knowledge.hubspot.com/articles/kcs_article/account/how-does-hubspot-track-visitors) tracks visitors by using browser cookies. Visitors will be tracked anonymously before they pro-actively provide their personal information through one of our lead generation forms.
  * [LinkedIn](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy) and [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/) track visitors anonymously. This means that third parties, including Facebook, may use cookies, web beacons and other storage technologies to collect and/or receive information from our website and elsewhere on the internet, and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads.

We consider LinkedIn, Facebook, Google and HubSpot to be third-party data processors. 

Why  
The purpose for collecting website visits data is to measure website traffic and better understand how visitors are interacting with its pages so we can improve user experience and the content we offer.

When it comes to LinkedIn and [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/business/learn/facebook-ads-pixel) tracking, cookies are also used to show personalized and relevant advertising while visitors are not on our website – including remarketing. 

Controlling Cookies  
Disabling cookies on your internet browser will prevent engagement tracking on the above-mentioned websites. You can learn how to manage cookies [here](https://www.aboutcookies.org/). You can opt-out of targeted advertising from networks KRT Marketing may work with by setting your preferences here: <http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/>; if you are within the European Union, you may visit: <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>

Email Links  
If you contact us via email by clicking on links [like this](mailto:info@krtmarketing.com) or [this](mailto:careers@krtmarketing.com) on our websites, your information will not be stored by the website. The data will be sent over Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP). Our email solution is through Microsoft Office 365. On the other hand, your information will be stored at HubSpot (see more info below) if you contact us via a website Contact form. 

##### INBOUND DATA COLLECTION

Some information on our website is gated – which means it requires visitors to provide their personal data (typically name, company and email address – but not limited to this information) in order to access resources on our websites. If you choose to provide us with your information, your data will not be stored by a website database or a local computer – it will automatically be forwarded and stored by [HubSpot](https://www.hubspot.com/security) (serves as CRM and inbound marketing automation platform) and/or [MailChimp](https://mailchimp.com/about/security/) (serves as email marketing platform) and/or [JotForm](https://www.jotform.com/security/) (serves as form creation and submission software). 

KRT Marketing will have access to your information in HubSpot, MailChimp and JotForm. We may use these platforms to send you regular recruitment marketing communications. All the information (data) submitted by you will be stored in HubSpot’s database for the duration of our contract with HubSpot, or until you actively request removal from the database. The information in MailChimp and JotForm will be stored in the respective databases for a maximum of three (3) years.

How this information will be used:  
We may send you emails about the recruitment marketing industry, including (but not limited to) articles, links, event invitations and KRT Marketing service communications. You can unsubscribe from these emails at any time.

We may contact you via email or phone with service information and offers.

By submitting your personal information, you give your consent to use that information as described in this privacy policy. If you’d like to revoke your consent at any time, you can do so by following the instructions listed in the ‘How to Request That We Stop Communication’ section below. 

##### JOB APPLICATIONS

KRT Marketing works with [SmartRecruiters](https://www.smartrecruiters.com/legal/general-privacy-policy/) to host our open job descriptions and candidate application submissions. Qualified applicants will have their personal data (including resumes) attached to emails that will be sent out internally to relevant KRT team members involved in the hiring process.

* * *

### HOW TO REQUEST THAT WE STOP COMMUNICATION

* * *

The following are ways you can request to stop receiving KRT communications: 

  1. Click on the unsubscribe link located in all our electronic newsletter communications;
  2. Manage your communication preferences
  3. Or email us requesting removal of your data from our databases (please include the email address that is subscribed to our mailing list in your email)

* * *

### HOW WE STORE AND TRANSFER DATA

* * *

No personally identifiable data is stored on any local computers.

Client campaign data is stored on our local Windows server and/or third-party services like Box or Google Drive. Transfers of campaign data is done through secure third-party services like Box, Google Drive or other services previously agreed upon with the client.

Our website hosting server  
Krtmarketing.com and its affiliated sites are hosted by [Bluehost](https://www.bluehost.com/terms/privacy-policy)  
Our storage hosting server  
Microsoft Windows Server 2012R2 server. Server receives regular updates provided by Microsoft. Data on this server is not encrypted at rest.  
Our email hosting server  
Microsoft Office 365  
Others  
Box  
Google Drive  
JotForm

* * *

### KRT MARKETING’S DATA PROCESSORS PRIVACY POLICIES

* * *

### HOW TO CONTACT US ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY

* * *

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or our practices, you can contact us at:

Email: [privacy@krtmarketing.com](mailto:privacy@krtmarketing.com)

Mailing Address:  
3685 Mount Diablo Blvd.,  
Suite 255,  
Lafayette, CA 94549  
Effective Date: May 25, 2018
